Dare to dream
The Long Game is a drama, family film directed by Julio Quintana.
In a segregated Texas, five Mexican-American teenage caddies were
prohibited from playing at the country club where they worked.
Against all odds, they formed their own team, built a one-hole course in
the fields, and won the 1957 Texas State championship.
Based on a true story.
JB Peña, played by Jay Hernandez.
Frank Mitchell, played by Dennis Quaid.
Pollo, played by Cheech Marin.
Joe Treviño, played by Julian Works.
Lucy Peña, played by Jaina Lee Ortiz.
Judge Milton Cox, played by Brett Cullen.
The Long Game is a 2023 American historical sports drama film directed by Julio
Quintana, who co-wrote the screenplay with Paco Farias and Jennifer C.
Stetson, based on Humberto G.
Garcia's 2010 non-fiction book Mustang Miracle.
The film stars Jay Hernandez, Julian Works, Jaina Lee Ortiz, Brett Cullen, Oscar Nuñez,
Paulina Chávez, Gregory Diaz IV, José Julián, Cheech Marin, and Dennis Quaid.
The Long Game premiered at the 2023 South by Southwest Film & TV Festival, and was
released theatrically in the United States by Mucho Mas Media on April 12, 2024.
The film explores themes of texas, golf, based on
true story, mexican american, 1950s.
The tone is emotional.